Privacy Policy
--------------

### Learn how we protect your privacy.

In a nutshell...
----------------

WindowsLogic Productions cares about your privacy and likes to let you know what data we have or haven't got about you. In a nutshell, we do not collect any data which you don't want us to have and disposes of useable data after a 30 day period if you do want us to use your data. Usable data is used to improve our website, applications and services so we can provide you with the best possible experience. WLP Cloud content is never used or fed to artificial intelligence for the purpose of improving our services.

1\. Sharing Information
-----------------------

WindowsLogic Productions does not share any personal information you give us with anyone. IP addresses and domains are kept private, but can be reported to authorities if they are attacking the services directly.

2\. Information Collection & Your Rights
----------------------------------------

When contacting us or sending a form on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address and other details to help you with your experience, this data is recorded and sent to us but is deleted after it has been read and/or dealt with and kept for no more than a maximum of 30 days if specified.

### Right of Subject Access

If you wish to access or export any of your personal data, then please [contact us](https://windowslogic.co.uk/contact.php). Your data will be sent to the email provided within 24 hours.

### Right to Be Informed

You have the right to be informed about any data collection and use of personal data, the reasons for processing it and who can see it.

### Right of Rectification

You have the right to ask for data to be put right if the data is inaccurate or incomplete.

### Right of Erasure

You have the right to request if information is removed if it is no longer needed or used.

### Right to Restrict Processing

The right in some curcumstances, to prevent the processing of personal information if it will cause damage or distress.

### Right to Object

The right to object to the processing of information (unless legitimate grounds for the processing are demonstrated that over-ride the interests, rights and freedom of the individual.)

### Right to Portability

The right to receive information in an electronic format.

### Other Information

WindowsLogic Productions will endeavour to ensure that information is kept accurate at all times.

We place a high value on the importance of information security and have a number of procedures in place to minimise the possibility of a compromise in data security.

3\. Using "Cookies"
-------------------

We do not use cookies for tracking purposes, session or any type of data collection, analytics or statistics. When using our WLP Cloud service, this section uses cookies for log-in and/or sesssion, but these are encrypted and are not stored server-side.

4\. Third Party Disclosure
--------------------------

We do not send any information to third parties or get information from any third parties, all data put into this website is completely private and no one has the ability to look or get hold of it. All data is encrypted in AES-256-CBC and is kept local and based around the WindowsLogic Productions servers, no personal data is leaked by us and is confidential.

5\. Third Party Links
---------------------

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party products or services have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked products or services. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these products or services.

6\. Privacy Policy Changes & Data Breach
----------------------------------------

When we update our privacy policy, we will notify our users within 72 hours period so that they have time to decide whether to continue using our services or not.

In event of a data breach whereby user data or organisation data is leaked, we will notify users within 72 hours of the breach occuring so they have time to change emails, passwords and allow users to download their data should they wish to use another service.

7\. Usable Data
---------------

Usable data is data you specify for us to keep when you write in forms that we provide for the purposes of contacting us and feedback. This data is only retaind for 30 days at maximum.

8\. WindowsLogic Productions Game Services
------------------------------------------

When launching and running our games (software), you are required to connect to the WindowsLogic Productions Game Services for the game (software) to check for updates. WindowsLogic Productions Game Services do not contain any personal information or store any analytical data from launcher, running and/or playing our games (software).

9\. WindowsLogic Productions Cloud
----------------------------------

Data you upload to this service will be kept indefinitely until you delete it via your account. WindowsLogic Productions retains account credentials and data in AES-256-CBC encryption. Account passwords can be changed via your account menu and account data can be deleted on request. WindowsLogic Productions does not retain any account data once deleted via a WLP Cloud account. IP addresses are retained only when you use the service and are deleted once you end your session. Authentication is handled under our usual security practices whereby no tokens are used and everything stays client-side. If you would like to download your account data in its entirety, you can do so by clicking "Zip" in your account folder. Users who are not registered and users with accounts can upload to a [Public](https://cloud.windowslogic.co.uk/public) folder whereby anyone can share the content held within and outside the Internet at their own descretion, WindowsLogic Productions holds no liability to what content is uploaded via the [Public](https://cloud.windowslogic.co.uk/public) folder. Users registered and/or unregistered cannont delete content uploaded to the [Public](https://cloud.windowslogic.co.uk/public) folder, content will only be deleted if reported or of our own descretion.

_Document created: 14/05/11 (14th May 2011)_
--------------------------------------------

﻿  

Copyright © 2011 - 2024 WindowsLogic Productions. All rights reserved.

All other trademarks and copyrights are the property of their respective owners. All rights reserved.

[Donate](https://www.paypal.com/donate?hosted_button_id=8TE9GD6PAGB8Q) / [Privacy Policy](https://windowslogic.co.uk/privacy-policy.php) / [Terms](https://windowslogic.co.uk/terms.php) / [Software Agreement](https://windowslogic.co.uk/appagreement.php) / [Feedback](https://windowslogic.co.uk/feedback.php) / [Social Links](https://social.windowslogic.co.uk/)
